Finding Aid for Institute of Gerontology (University of Michigan) records 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Programs, Projects, Studies, Curricula 1942-1984
  One of the most important curricula in the IoG was the Specialists in Aging Training program. This program had two facets: a long-term master's degree curricula and a short-term residential institute leading to a certificate of specialization. Additional information regarding the Residential Institute will be found in the separate collection of Woodrow Hunter's papers. A less significant, but still noteworthy, project was the Senior Sounds radio program on WUOM, the transcripts for which are contained in this series (tapes of these shows may be found in the library's collection of WUOM, Tapes, B Series). Three other radio programs produced by IoG are represented in the Sound Tapes series in this collection.
  - Biology of Aging (file of Harold Johnson)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, 1978-79 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, Memos, Reports, and Supporting Documents
      - 1974-75 (Box 5)
      - 1976-77 (Box 5)
      - 1978-79 (Box 5)
      - 1979-consultant (Box 5)
      - 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - Research (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education Program: Report 1978 (Box 5)
  - Dissertations
    - Effect of Perceived Age on Initial Impressions and Normative Role Expectations (Box 5)
    - Comparison of Demographic, Social, and Political Characteristics Between Old Age Group Identifiers and Nonidentifiers (Box 5)
  - Educational Gerontology Graduate Program (file of David Peterson) circa 1970-1974
    - Proposals, Announcements, Course Descriptions (Box 5)
    - Relevant Minutes and Committee Memos, 1970-71 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence 1970-1974 (Box 5)
    - Students-Memos to and Lists of (Box 5)
    - Notes (Box 5)
  - Health Advocacy for Older People, Jackson County, 1980-81
    - Project Synopsis (Box 5)
    - Quarterly Reports to Community Services Administration (Box 5)
    - Minutes and Notes of Meetings
      - Planning Committee (Box 5)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 5)
      - Technical Advisory Committee (Box 5)
      - Meetings with Outside Agencies (Box 5)
    - Correspondence
      - Interoffice Memos (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Interpersonal Skills Section of "Blue Training Manual" (Box 5)
    - Resource People (Box 5)
    - Peer Advocate Training Program-"The Mature Volunteer" (Box 6)
      - Peer Counselors/Advocates (Box 6)
      - Enrolled Volunteers and Intro Session September 24, 1980 (Box 6)
      - October 10, 1980 Session (Box 6)
      - October 28, November 4, November 11, November 18, November 25, December 2, 1980 Sessions (Box 6)
      - December 9, 1980 Session (Box 6)
      - December 16, 1980January 9, January 13, January 20, January 27, February 3, February 10, February 17, 1981 Sessions (Box 6)
      - February 20, 1981 Session (Box 6)
      - February 24, March 3, March 10, 1981 Sessions (Box 6)
      - March 24, 1981 Session (Box 6)
      - March 31, 1981 Session (Box 6)
      - April 7, May 5, May 12, May 28, 1981 Sessions (Box 6)
      - Evaluations (Box 6)
    - Public Workshops and Lectures
      - Home Visitation, July 30 (Box 6)
      - Medigap, August 27 (Box 6)
      - Sleep, Lifestyle, September 29 (Box 6)
      - Medicare, November 7 (Box 6)
    - Health Education Programs, How to Implement (Box 6)
    - Publicity
      - Radio Interview December, 1980 (Box 6)
      - Clippings (Box 6)
    - Literature
      - Unpublished Analysis (Box 6)
      - Consumer Pamphlets (Box 6)
      - Turner Geriatric Clinic Programs (Box 6)
      - "Nelvia's Pamphlets" (Box 6)
    - Washtenaw County Community Services for and Needs of the Elderly (Box 6)
    - Peer Counseling Programs (Box 6)
    - Bibliographies (Box 6)
    - Alcoholism and Aging (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Immunoglobin Levels, Study of 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Low Income Housing for the Elderly Demonstration Project (Lurie Terrace), 1964-65 (Box 6)
  - Luella Harrison Memorial Home 1965 (Box 6)
  - Management of Housing for the Elderly, Short Course in 1966 (Box 6)
  - Milieu Therapy Training Program 1964-1975
    - 1964 Proposal (Box 6)
    - 1968-1970 Budget Information (Box 6)
    - 1973-74: Summary of Progress, New Proposal, Rejection, and Response (Box 6)
    - 1974 Proposal (Box 7)
    - 1975 Proposal: Use of Media to Improve Geriatric Treatment Centers (Box 7)
  - "Planning for Aging," Report 1973 (Box 7)
  - Quality of Teacher Worklife (co-sponsored by School of Education) 1981
    - Proposal, Progress Reports, Related Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Secondary Material (Box 7)
  - Senate Special Committee on the Problems of Aging, Study of, 1969-70 (Box 7)
  - "Senior Sounds": Series of Radio Programs for WUOM 1973-1981
    - Script Lists
      - Chronological (Box 7)
      - Subject (Distribution List) (Box 7)
    - Scripts
      - 1973 (Box 7)
      - 1974 (Box 7)
      - 1975 (Box 7)
      - 1976 (Box 7)
      - 1977 (Box 7)
      - 1978 (Box 7)
      - 1979 (Box 7)
      - 1980 (Box 7)
      - 1981 (Box 7)
  - Short Films-Milieu Therapy and Senior Citizen Housing, 1969-70 (Box 8)
  - Spatial Privacy and Territoriality Among the Elderly 1968 (Box 8)
  - Specialists in Aging-Training Programs 1967-1977
    - 1967-1969
      - Report of Progress (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, Financial Information, Grant Renewal (Box 8)
      - Long-term (Master's Degree) Program (Box 8)
      - Short-term (Residential Institute) Program (Box 8)
    - 1971-1977
      - Grant Application, Including Program Summary 1971 (Box 8)
      - Brochures, Mailings, and Other Information re: 1975, 1976 Residential Institute (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous Information re: 1977 Long-term Program (Box 8)
  - Training Programs in Michigan Colleges and Universities 1969-1971
    - Proposals (Box 8)
    - Financial Information (Box 8)
  - Ypsilanti State Hospital Internship Program, 1967-68 (Box 8)
  - American Values and the Elderly. Project final report December 31, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Continuing education programs (Box 15)
  - Course descriptions (Box 15)
  - Curricula (Box 15)
  - Curriculum Committee 1975-1978 (Box 15)
  - Directory of Graduates, Residential Institutes in Aging 1967-1974 (Box 16)
  - Educational Unit on Aging for High Schools (Box 16)
  - IoG Training Courses (Box 16)
  - Learning for Living Extension Course 1942 (Box 16)
  - Milieu Therapy Project
    - Center for Training in, and program design June 1974 (Box 16)
    - Final Report (Box 16)
    - Progress Reports 1964-1967, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Staff papers 1966-1978, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Training programs and materials (Box 16)
  - Preretirement Education Training Program 1977 (Box 16)
  - Project charts
    - 1975-1979 (Box 16)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 16)
  - Project files summary (Box 16)
  - Project proposals 1961-1978
    - 1961 An experimental research-demonstration project in the rehabilitation of recent first-admission geriatric mental hospital patients (Box 16)
    - 1969-1970
      - Development of training programs in Michigan colleges and universities (Box 16)
      - Faculty seminar in social gerontology (Box 16)
      - Orientation and technical assistance workshops (Box 16)
  - Project proposals 1961-1978
    - 1970
      - Protecting the elderly: The need, techniques and consequences of intervention (Box 16)
      - Training for specialists in aging (Box 16)
    - 1970-1971 Development of training programs in Michigan colleges and universities (Box 16)
    - 1971
      - Aged patients and nursing home services (Box 16)
      - Senior consumer education project (Box 16)
    - 1972
      - Educational television programming for the aged (Box 16)
      - Forced relocation. (Box 16)
      - Orientation workshops in services to the aging (Box 16)
      - Planning and service area leadership training program (Box 16)
      - Training for specialists in aging (Box 16)
      - Workshops in public housing for the elderly (Box 16)
      - Survey: Nursing home resident needs (Box 16)
      - Training of older persons for community action roles (Box 16)
    - 1973-1974 Training for specialists in aging (continuation) (Box 16)
    - 1978 The effect of retirement on the welfare of Americans; analyses of the longitudinal retirement history survey (Box 16)
  - Project Reports (Box 17)
    - Development of post retirement education models with a community college consortium on aging-final report 1976 (Box 17)
    - Factors influencing the abandoning of private homes by the elderly-final report 1977 (Box 17)
    - Employee benefits and the older worker-preliminary report 1984 (Box 17)
  - Project TAP 1973, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Residential Institutes in Aging (Box 17)
  - Spanish-speaking elderly in Michigan-a summer study project circa 1970s (Box 17)
  - Study of the needs of older people living in Grand Rapids 1953 (Box 17)
  - Summer Institute in Gerontology (Box 17)
  - Summer Institute on Social Gerontology 1973 (Box 17)
  - Western Michigan University, Development of training programs project, by Ellen Robin 1970 (Box 17)
  - Winter workshop (Box 17)
- Unfunded Programs, Projects, Studies, and Curricula 1964-1971
  The Unfunded Programs, Projects, Studies, and Curricula, 1964-1977 series documents proposals which, for one reason or another, never got off the ground. They remain important because they reflect additional concerns of the institute staff. Indeed, the fact that these projects did not receive funding is not necessarily an accurate reflection of their worth. In any case, failures may be as informative as successes in studying the history of an institute and of a profession.
  - Aged Patients and Nursing Home Services 1969 (Box 8)
  - Alternative Long-term Care Settings, Feasibility and Cost Effectiveness of 1974 (Box 8)
  - Alternative Modes of Long-term Adult Day Care 1974 (Box 8)
  - Developing Active Participation of the Aging in Control of Hypertension 1973 (Box 8)
  - Housing Management Trainee Program 1966 (Box 8)
  - Library Services to the Aged 1974 (Box 8)
  - Mental Health and Aging, Training for 1974 (Box 8)
  - Pedestrians, Provisions for Elderly and Handicapped 1974 (Box 8)
  - Service Needs and Help Giving Potential of the Aged, Study of 1973 (Box 8)
  - University Retirement Community, 1976-77 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
- Ann Arbor Veterans Administration (AAVA) Hospital 1976-1981
  The bulk of the Ann Arbor Veterans Administration Hospital, 1976-1981 material concerns the Hospital's Geriatric Research, Education and Clinical Center (GRECC). Harold Johnson, co-director of the IoG, was one of several individuals from outside the hospital to be consulted on the development of the GRECC proposal. The hospital hoped to involve the university community as a whole in the center; the object was to provide holistic care and to integrate research and treatment.
  - General Correspondence 1976-1981 (Box 8)
  - Geriatric Research, Education and Clinical Center (GRECC) (Box 9)
    - Proposals 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Correspondence and Supporting Documents (Box 9)
- Miscellaneous Files 1956-1985
  Miscellaneous Files, 1956-1981 includes material on a variety of institute and staff activities. Most noteworthy are the folders for the institute's Learning Resource Center (Library). Included in those folders are lists of IoG publications and lists of the Annual Conferences on Aging for which published proceedings and/or papers exist. Also worth remarking in the series are a few short addresses and articles by Wilma Donahue, scattered documents concerning the origins of both the Michigan Society of Gerontology and the Michigan Commission on Aging, some statistics on the elderly of Washtenaw County, and some correspondence with two visiting scholars from Eastern Europe. Additional scattered correspondence with visiting scholars may be found in the portion of the Other Conferences and Symposia series relating to Wilma Donahue.
  - Institute of Gerontology
    - Learning Resource Center
      - Annual Reports, Acquisition Reports, etc. 1971-1980 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence, Papers, and Undated Miscellaneous, 1972-1980 (Box 9)
    - Wilma Donahue Writings (see also Sound Tapes series) (Box 9)
  - News Releases and Clippings 1966-1968
    - Special Projects
      - Visiting Scholars
        - Dr. A. Civea (Hungary) 1969 (Box 9)
        - Dr. L. Dobrowolski (Poland) 1969 (Box 9)
      - "Medigame" Critique (Box 9)
    - Michigan Association of Gerontology Students (MAGS) (Box 9)
    - Public Policy and Aging: Syllabi 1970 (Box 9)
    - Staff and Student Directory undated (Box 9)
  - Gerontology
    - "Gerontologists as Consultants and Researchers", 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Michigan Society of Gerontology: Founding 1956 (Box 9)
    - Gerontological Society: Public Policy Committee Reports and Memos 1969 (Box 9)
  - Aging and the Elderly
    - Michigan Commission on Aging (MCA): Wilma Donahue File
      - Creation: Testimony, Memos, and Supporting Documents 1965 (Box 9)
      - Review of Funded Projects 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Washtenaw County Elderly: Statistics on and Needs of 1970-1973 (Box 9)
    - Nursing Home Residential Care 1971 (Box 9)
    - Secondary Source Material
      - Cable TV Projects (Box 9)
      - "Economic Security for the Aged in the U.S. and Canada," 1956 (Box 9)
      - Housing, Health (Box 10)
      - Information Referral Services-out-of-state (Box 10)
      - "Michigan Comprehensive Plan on Aging, 1974" (Box 10)
      - Nutrition (Box 10)
      - From Senior Power Day 1981 (Box 10)
      - Social Security Opinion Survey, Brookings Institute 1973 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Draft of Report of Professional Skills Alliance to New Detroit, Inc. (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Aging and Mental Health Advisory Group (Box 20)
  - Area agencies on aging (Box 20)
  - Child and Family Service of Washtenaw [County] (Box 20)
  - Citizens Committee for Economic, Inc., programs (Box 20)
  - Eastern Michigan University (Box 20)
  - Foundations for Establishing Education Program Standards in Gerontology 1977-1979, 4 folders (Box 20)
    (Association for Gerontology in Higher Education and the Gerontological Society Collaborative Project, Harold Johnson, Chair)
  - Geriatric Education Center, 1983- (Box 20)
  - Gerontology at Michigan, Autumn-Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Greater Detroit Area Health Council (Box 20)
  - Home Health Aides (Box 20)
  - Hospices (Box 20)
  - Hunter, Woodrow W., awards file 1977-1985 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg International Scholarship Program on Health and Aging (Box 20)
  - Local Committees on Aging in Michigan June 1958 (Box 20)
  - MAGS (Michigan Association of Gerontology Students) (Box 20)
  - MAGS Newsletter, vol. 1, no. 1- February 1974-May 1983 (Box 20)
  - Michigan Society of Gerontology (Box 20)
  - Michigan State University (Box 20)
  - National Archive of Computerized Data on Aging [NACDA] Newsletter/Bulletin July 1978-January 1983 (Box 20)
  - Placement Service in Aging (Box 20)
  - Project Transition, Inc. 1979-1980 (Box 20)
  - Report to the Legislature 1972 (Box 20)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation (Box 20)
  - Senior Citizens Broadcasting Group, programs, etc (Box 20)
  - Social Security Enactment 1935 miscellaneous reports, speeches (Box 20)
  - Task Force on Older Americans 1965-1968 (Box 20)
  - Teaching-Learning Communities, Ann Arbor Public Schools 1976-1978 (Box 20)
  - Television series 1979 (Box 20)
  - Testimony before U.S. Congress (Box 20)
  - Title IVA Course, "Aging and services to the aging" (Box 20)
  - UAW (Box 20)
  - Washtenaw County Community Mental Health Center (Box 20)
  - Washtenaw County Council on Aging (Box 20)
- Executive Board 1969-1987
  After the early meetings, which sought to hammer out the details of the new institute, the Executive Board Minutes, 1969-1987, shed little light on any but the routine bureaucratic functions of the IoG. Like most executive board minutes, they report only actions taken and resolutions adopted; they give little information about the discussions surrounding a given proposal.
  - Members 1977-1982 (Box 12)
  - Minutes
    - 1965-1971 (Box 1)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 12)
    - 1971 (Box 12)
    - 1972 (Box 12)
    - 1973 (Box 13)
    - 1974 (Box 13)
    - 1975 (Box 13)
    - 1976 (Box 13)
    - 1977 (Box 13)
    - 1978 (Box 13)
    - 1979 (Box 13)
    - 1980 (Box 13)
    - 1981 (Box 13)
    - 1983 (Box 13)
    - 1984 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1974-1980 (Box 13)
    - 1981-1987 (Box 13)
    - Strategic Retreat with the Office of Academic Affairs 1987 (Box 1)
- Publications
  The Publications series includes published articles, staff papers, reports, bibliographies published or produced by the IoG
  - "Across the generations: Equity and harmony as policy goals". 1983 (Box 17)
  - Aging in American Society, J. D. Manney, Jr. 1975 (Box 17)
  - Aging in the Modern World, Series 1956 8 booklets (Box 17)
  - Aging Related Research at the University of Michigan. [various titles] 1974, 1979, 1980, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Alcohol, drugs and aging: Usage and Problems Series, no. 1 1980 (Box 17)
  - Apartments for independent handicapped elderly 1977 (Box 17)
  - "Area planning for the aging", by Armand Lauffer 1974 (Box 17)
  - Benedict, Bob, ["American Indian aged"] (Box 17)
    ([n.d., mimeo., 10 pp)
  - Bibliographies
    - Aging in rural settings (Box 17)
    - Alcoholism among the elderly (Box 17)
    - Educational gerontology, Parts 1-20 August 1971 (Box 17)
    - Environment and behavior (Box 17)
    - Nursing homes and care of the geriatric patient (Box 17)
    - Older people and the church (Box 17)
    - Older workers: An untapped resource (Box 17)
    - Preparation for retirement (Box 17)
    - Retirement (Box 17)
    - Role and training of professional personnel in aging (Box 17)
  - Catalogs of IOG publications (Box 18)
  - Catawba [Va.] Hospital handbook for facilitators, by F. E. Grant 1976 (Box 18)
  - A collection of cartoons; a way of examining practices in a treatment center, Lena Metzelaar, comp. 1975 (Box 18)
  - Currently at IOG April 1975-June 1979 (Box 18)
  - "Death and dying", questionnaire (Box 18)
  - Directory of gerontological libraries and resource centers in the United States: a preliminary draft (Box 18)
  - Effective social services for older Americans, by S.S. Tobin, S.M. Davidson, and A. Sack 1976 (Box 18)
  - Energy dependence and vulnerability to increases in home heating costs of the rural elderly 1982 (Box 18)
  - Fact sheets (Box 18)
  - Faculty seminar in social gerontology: A model for the expansion of gerontological instruction, by David A. Peterson, Wilma Donahue, and Clark Tibbitts 1971 (Box 18)
  - Gerontology: A cross-national core list of significant works..., by W.M. Edwards and F. Flynn 1982 (Box 18)
  - Gerontology libraries survey 1971-1974 (Box 18)
  - Gerontology Quarterly, no. 1, Fall 1973 (Box 18)
    [no other issued]
  - Gottesman, Leonard E. [bibliography of his writings] 1960-1969 (Box 18)
  - Government and social welfare goals for 1993, by Wayne Vasey circa 1973 (Box 18)
  - Graduate education in aging within the social sciences, edited by R.E. Kushner and M.E. Bunch 1967 (Box 18)
  - Growing old in America's cities, edited by L.A. Pastalan and Wilma Donohue., 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Guide to agency development for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to advisory groups for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to advocacy for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to building community awareness for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to fiscal management for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to grantmanship for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to information and referral systems for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to PERT for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to program resources for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guide to sources of information for area planners in aging, Project TAP 1974 (Box 18)
  - Guidelines for a telephone reassurance service 1973 (Box 18)
  - Health advocacy for older people 1981 (Box 18)
  - History, current status, and future of the Administration on Aging's Title V training grant program, report February 1969 (Box 18)
  - Home remedies and the black elderly, by E.L. Boyd, L.A. Shimp, and M.J. Hackney 1984 (Box 18)
  - IOG Consumer Education Staff, Spanish language leaflets for consumers (Box 18)
  - The Institute of Gerontology at the University of Michigan 1975-1980 (Box 18)
  - Issues in health care containment: A profile of the elderly consumer (Box 18)
  - Key concepts in aging (Box 18)
  - Living arrangements for older people in Southeastern Michigan November 1972 (Box 18)
  - Looking forward to retirement (Box 18)
  - Manuscripts, unpublished 1972-1974 (Box 18)
  - Media resources for gerontology 1977 (Box 18)
  - Michigan Collegiate Gerontology Newsletter (Box 18)
    vol. 1, no. 1 (April 1970)-vol. 2, no. 6 (April 1972)
    [incomplete]
  - Michigan Facts on Aging, no. 1-no. 3 March 1967-February 1969 (Box 18)
  - Newsletter 1981 (Box 18)
  - Nurse aide training program for Michigan nursing homes 1981 (Box 18)
  - Occasional Papers in Gerontology, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Older driver refresher course-instructor handbook 1976 (Box 18)
  - Older people in the Detroit area and the retirement age; a study of a cross-section of the over-65 group of citizens (Box 18)
  - The older worker in an aging society; a special report 1981 (Box 18)
  - A Pathfinder service: developing a driving route orientation program (Box 18)
  - Patients in Michigan's nursing homes..., by J.L. Barney 1973 (Box 18)
  - Perceptions of age, questionnaire (Box 18)
  - A perspective on aging for area planners (Box 18)
  - The political sociology of Ludwig Gomplowicz with a translation of "Outlines of Social Philosophy (Box 18)
    tr. by Joseph Bunzel, manuscript
  - Protecting the vulnerable adult, by E.J. Ferguson 1978 (Box 18)
  - Relocation Reports 1-3 (Box 18)
  - Research and Report Series, no. 5, "Community college services for senior citizens" November 1971 (Box 18)
  - Resources in Aging, "The process of change", by D.H. Coons, no. 1 1973 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "Two years with eighty patients", by V. LaRue, no. 2 1973 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "Social interaction groups in a therapeutic community", by L. Metzelaar, no. 3 1973 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "The end of the line", a simulation game developed by F.L. Goodman, no. 4 1975 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "To live with dignity", by M-F. Boudreault, V. LaRue, and L. Metzelaar, [no. 5?] 1975 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "Humanistic perspectives in aging", annotated bibliography 1976 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging, "Views of aging; a teacher's guide", by M.J. Cameron 1976 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging Series, "Past Sixty: The older woman in print and film", by C. Hollenshead 1977 (Box 19)
  - Resources in Aging Series, "Gerontology: A core list of significant works" 1978 (Box 19)
  - Result of a study tour of European industrial therapy programs..., by D.H. Coons circa 1964 (Box 19)
  - Retirement options; a gerontological simulation, leader's manual 1979 (Box 19)
  - Retirement planning resource materials 1981 (Box 19)
  - Sources of information for people working in the field of gerontology, revised January 1974 (Box 19)
  - Staff papers I, authors: Bourestom; Breslow; Bykowski; Calhoun (Box 19)
  - Staff papers II, authors: Ciarolo; Cohen; Coons; Dickerson; Fairchild; Felton; Gibson; Gottesman; Gutmann; Huber; Jackson; Kastenbaum (Box 19)
  - Staff papers III, authors: Kahana; McClusky; Maney; Miller (Box 19)
  - Staff papers IV, authors: Olariu; Pastalan; Parrish; Prakken (Box 20)